mmgn.com 2014-11-30

# MMGN Privacy Policy

## What is the Privacy Policy about?

MMGN.com ('MMGN') is operated and owned MMGN.com Pty Ltd (ACN 149 673 183) ('We' or 'us'). We take privacy obligations seriously and are committed to the responsible handling of personal information and protecting the privacy rights of individuals. This policy sets out how we handle your personal information. It explains the key measures that have been taken to make sure it abides by the Commonwealth Privacy Act 1998, which includes the 10 National Privacy Principles. As a condition of using the site, you agree to be bound by the terms of this Policy.

## Collection of information

The information we collect from you depends on how and why you access this web site. If you visit the web site to read, browse or download information, our computer system may record information about the visit such as the number of pages visited and the duration of the visit. Such information is only used for web site administration and it is not used to identify you. 

We ensure that personal information is collected by lawful and fair means with your consent. We only collect personal information from users during: 

  1. **Registration to MMGN**

When you register for membership on MMGN, we will ask you for your email address and certain demographic information such as your name, birth date, gender and location. Provision of a valid email address is necessary for first-time registered users to activate their accounts.

  2. **Participation in online features or services**

MGN also collect information about you when you voluntarily disclose them using the features and services of MMGN, such as writing reviews, updating your blog, participating in forum discussions and providing user surveys. Common examples are your game ownership, wish list, review opinions and feedback.

## Use and disclosure of information

We use your personal information in order to:

  * verify your identity;
  * respond to any queries or feedback you may have;
  * provide, administer and manage our services; and
  * gain an understanding of your information and communication needs in to improve the functionalities and services of MMGN.

Some of the outside organisations we may disclose your personal information to include:

  * our advertisers and sponsors;
  * credit reporting and fraud checking agencies;
  * our professional advisers, including our legal advisers and accountants; and
  * government and regulatory authorities, including the Australian Communications and Media Authority.

Below are more details about how we use your personal information and the specific circumstances under which your personal information may be disclosed.

  1. **Email Newsletters**

Users of MMGN are automatically registered to receive newsletters that we offer on a periodic basis. We do this to keep you informed of news, events, special offers, services or products that we believe you will find valuable. If you want to update your email address or stop receiving a newsletter, follow the procedures to unsubscribe at the bottom of any newsletter MMGN send you or simply visit the profile page to update your profile.

  2. **Co-registration with Other Sites**

To provide better user experiences, MMGN offers its users the ability to co-register with other web sites in the same network, which are 100 percent owned and managed by us. Currently it includes www.mypsp.com.au; www.mygames.com.au; www.mywii.com.au; www.myds.com.au; www.myps3.com.au; www.my360.com.au; www.mytelly.com.au; www.mybuzz.com.au; and www.mybluray.com.au. Registered users of MMGN are automatically registered as a member of the above-mentioned sites and your personal information will be shared by these web sites. If you wish to cancel your membership with these sites, simply advise MMGN administrators via email.

  3. **Advertisers.**

Registered users of MMGN may receive emails that MMGN send on behalf of our advertisers. MMGN will not disclose your personal information to the advertisers without your consent. You will only receive information from MMGN, not directly from the advertisers.

  4. **Surveys and User Research.**

MMGN conducts email and web-delivered surveys from time to time, as well as instant polls, to gather information about our users. Taking these surveys and polls is entirely optional. You have no obligation to respond to them. We share only the aggregate results of these surveys, not personal information, with our advertisers to help them better understand our services and monitor the reach of their advertising on our service. We also use some of the personal information that you provide in these surveys to help us understand your interests and to make MMGN more useful to you. 

## Cookies

Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to your computer for record keeping purposes. MMGN uses cookies to recognize registered users to the site and provide them a more seamless browsing experience. The third-party tools that MMGN utilises, including third-party advertisements and statistical tools, may also contain cookies. Most web browsers are set to accept cookies, but you may configure your browser to reject cookies, although it may interfere with some functionalities of the site. You can opt out of third party vendor’s cookies at any time by visiting this page: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

## Access, Correction and Update of Information

To access, correct or update your account or other personal information such as your location or interests, please use the "Edit Profile" page at the site on which you are registered.

If you have any other questions, comments or complaints regarding this Policy, please contact MMGN administrator via contact form.

## Storage and Security of Information

Your personal information is stored on MMGN computer servers. We endeavour to take all reasonable and appropriate steps to keep any information about our users secure. We protect your personal information with technical, administrative and physical safeguards to protect against loss, unauthorized access, destruction, misuse, modification and improper disclosure. Please however be aware that no computer system or information can ever be fully protected against every possible hazard.

## Change of Privacy Policy

The Policy is accessible from a link entitled "Privacy Policy" at the bottom of the MMGN home page. We will always respond to the feedback we get from users and will always be developing new features, functionalities, services and new ways of working. Because of this, this Policy is subject to change from time to time. If they do, we will publish the new version and make an announcement on the site. But we will not necessarily send you specific notice of any change. Users are recommended to check the site regularly for such announcements, and your continued use of the site will signify that you agree to these changes. Any changes we make will abide by the Privacy Act, and will continue to treat your personal information with respect.
